Guide to the Gay Cable Network Archives, 1982-2001 MSS.231
Fales Library and Special Collections
Gay Cable Network Archives
1982-2001
1984-2000
Fales Library and Special Collections
Gay Cable Network
MSS.231
400 Linear Feet (254 Boxes)
Founded in 1982 by Louis P. Maletta, the Gay Cable Network was the premiere media chronicler of events and personalities of the lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender (LGBT) community for nearly two decades. GCN programming broadcast on public access television in New York City and other major cities worldwide.
Conditions Governing Access
The following Series are unprocessed and currently unavailable to patrons:
Series V
Series VII
Series X
Series XIII
Series XIV
Series XV
Series XVI
Series XX
Series XXIX
Series XXXVI
Arrangement
This collection has been arranged into 36 Series:
Series I: About Entertainment
Series II: AIDS Memorial Quilt
Series III: Be Our Guest
Series IV: Candied Camera
Series V: Commercials, Trailers, and Miscellaneous Promos
Series VI: Dungeon Knights
Series VII: Emerald City
Series VIII: Events
Series IX: Frankie Loves Johnny
Series X: Gay Games and Sporting Events
Series XI: Gay USA
Series XII: Health and Fitness with Jessie Garcia
Series XIII: Interviews
Series XIV: In the Dungeon
Series XV: In the Life
Series XVI: Lavender Health
Series XVII: LGBT Parades, Marches, and Rallies
Series XVIII: Men & Films
Series XIX: Miscellaneous Programs and Clips
Series XX: Music Videos
Series XXI: Out on Wednesdays
Series XXII: Political Conventions
Series XXIII: Pride and Progress / The Right Stuff
Series XXIV: Public Service Announcements
Series XXV: Secret Passions
Series XXVI: Sixth Floor Harrison
Series XXVII: Sports Scan
Series XXVIII: Static
Series XXIX: Stonewall Place After Dark
Series XXX: Unedited Footage
Series XXXII: Lou Maletta and GCN Files
Oversize Series XXIX: Lou Maletta and GCN Files
Series XXXIII: Photographs
Series XXXIV: Objects
Oversize Series XXXV: Objects
Series XXXVI: Lou Maletta Interviews
Scope and Contents
The Gay Cable Network Archives contain video recordings of shows broadcast on Gay Cable Network (GCN), event recordings, and the network's photographs, merchandise, administrative files, and promotional materials. Although arranged in series by program, some videotapes are compilations containing multiple programs. In those cases, each program is listed in the title of the record.
Broadcast on public access television in New York City and other major cities worldwide, GCN covered key Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender, and Queer (LGBTQ) civil rights battles, five presidential conventions, as well as the AIDS pandemic and social protests often marginalized in the mainstream media. On televised programs like Gay USA, Pride and Progress, The Right Stuff, Men & Films, Candied Camera, In the Dungeon, and Lavender Health, GCN conducted numerous interviews with leading politicians, medical and educational professionals, entertainers, and social activists.
Historical Note
Under the direction of Lou Maletta, and broadcast on Manhattan Cable Television Channel 35, Gay Cable Network (GCN) began in 1982 and stopped production in 2001. GCN was the first network in the nation to openly appeal to a gay, lesbian, bisexual, and transgender audience. GCN initially broadcast a series titled "Men & Films," which explored the gay male image in media and male erotica, and the network soon evolved to host a wider variety of content, including news and current affairs programs which covered political developments affecting the LGBT community and the AIDS/HIV epidemic. Throughout its time, GCN provided coverage of the Democratic and Republican National Conventions, with on-floor correspondents interviewing candidates and delegates, as well as coverage of the 1987 and 1993 LGBT rights marches on Washington. A documentary aired on GCN, "Out in the 90's," earned the network a Special Recognition Award at the inaugural GLAAD Media Awards in 1990.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to some audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Audiovisual materials that have not been preserved may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Fales Library, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Louis P. Maletta in 2008. The accession number associated with this gift is 2008.231.
Gays -- Political activity -- New York (State) -- New York.; Video recordings -- Political aspects; Video recordings -- Social aspects.; Lesbians -- United States; Gays in popular culture.; Cable television; LGBTQ+ activism; Gay men.; Gay liberation movement.; Gay activists -- New York (State) -- New York.; Gay Men's Health Crisis, Inc.; Northrop, Ann; Humm, Andy; Maletta, Louis P.
- Series I: AbOUT Entertainment
  - AbOUT Entertainment Vol. I No. 1, [1995]; ID: 231.1186 (Box 77, Media ID: 231.1186)
    General
    Format: 3/4 in. Umatic
    Duration: 00:29:00
    Program content: Buster Hymen at MeowMix with Eileen Myles, Chrystal Balls-Search for Super-myrtle, Eclipse-Jeremy Podeswake
  - [1]--AbOUT Entertainment Vol. I No. 2 [2]--Health and Fitness with Jessie, 4/8, [1995]; ID: 231.1187 (Box 77, Media ID: 231.1187)
    TRT: [00:29:00]
    Program content: [1]--World AIDS Day, Nora Burns and Max Harold, Thomas Gaspar-Photographer, Christal Balls, Toys for Tots, Bambi Sue, Patrick Gilles
  - AbOUT Entertainment Vol. I No. 2, [1995]; ID: 231.1188 (Box 77, Media ID: 231.1188)
    Program content: World AIDS Day, Julie Wheeler at MeowMix with Buster Hymen, Chrystal Balls, Incomplete Tape
  - [1]--AbOUT Entertainment No. 3 [2]--Health and Fitness with Jessie, 3/11, [1995]; ID: 231.1189 (Box 77, Media ID: 231.1189)
    TRT: 00:30:00
    Program content: [1]--Christmas Show, Jeremy Helliger-Music, Mark Davis-Dance, Bambi Sue, Miriam Sarada-Bruce Spruce, Baby Jane Dexter, Lady Bunny-Varla Jean Mennan, Sherry Vine Jungle Belles
  - AbOUT Entertainment Vol. I No. 3, Second Copy, [1995]; ID: 231.1190 (Box 77, Media ID: 231.1190)
    TRT: [00:30:00]
  - AbOUT Entertainment No. 4, January 1996, ID: 231.1191 (Box 77, U-matic ID: 231.1191)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Duration: 30 minutes.
    Scope and Contents
    Program content: Julie Wheeler and Buster Hymen, Miriam Saroda-David Gurland, Patrick Gilles, John Cameron Mitchell-Hedwig, Michael Fitzgerald-Frozen Belts-Seth Cohen?
  - AbOUT Entertainment Vol. I No. 5, First Copy, [1996]; ID: 231.1192 (Box 77, Media ID: 231.1192)
  - [1]--AbOUT Entertainment Vol. I No. 5 [2]--Health and Fitness with Jessie, 5/6, [1996]; ID: 231.1193 (Box 77, U-matic ID: 231.1193)
    Program content: [1]--Miriam Saroda, Lou Maletta, Buster Hymen with Shelly Marz at The Kitchen, Mapplethorpe Exhibit - Children, Colin Martin
  - [1]--AbOUT Entertainment Vol. I No. 5, Second Copy [2]--AbOUT Entertainment No. 6 [3]--Health and Fitness with Jessie, 4/29, [1996]; ID: 231.1194 (Box 77, U-matic ID: 231.1194)
    Program content: [2]--Miriam Saroda and Max Harold, Lou Maletta, Buster Hymen with Shelly Marz, Mapplethorpe, Max Makeover, Colin Martin
  - AbOUT Entertainment, Undated; ID: 231.1195 (Box 77, Media ID: 231.1195)
    Program content: Comedy, Fashion, Crystal Bal, Buster Hymen
  - AbOUT Entertainment, [1995]; ID: 231.1196 (Box 77, Media ID: 231.1196)
    Program content: Tomas Gaspar-An American Family
  - AbOUT Entertainment Opening, Undated; ID: 231.1197 (Box 77, Media ID: 231.1197)
    Program content: About Cabaret
  - AbOUT Entertainment Opening Title, [1995]; ID: 231.1198 (Box 77, Media ID: 231.1198)
  - AbOUT Entertainment Intro, Theme Song, Etc., [1995]; ID: 231.1199 (Box 77, Media ID: 231.1199)
- Series II: AIDS Memorial Quilt
  Scope and Content
  Titles have been transcribed from original container annotations. These tapes have not been viewed by an archivist.
  - Names Project, August 12, 1987; ID: 231.1630 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1630)
    Duration: Unknown
  - Quilt at the Elipse - Tape Number 1, October 8, 1988; ID: 231.1631A (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1631A)
  - [1]--Quilt at the Elipse - Tape Number 2 [2]--Number 15, October 8, 1988; ID: 231.1632 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1632)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Currently not available for viewing.
  - Candlelight March - Tape Number 3, October 8, 1988; ID: 231.1633 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1633)
  - Candlelight March - Tape Number 4, October 8, 1988; ID: 231.1634 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1634)
  - [1]--Quilt-Lincoln Memorial and B-roll - Tape Number 5 [2]--Gay Cable Network - Number 3, October 8-9, 1988; ID: 231.1635 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1635)
  - The Quilt, Washington D.C., October 8, 1988; ID: 231.1636A (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1636A)
    Format: VHS
  - Dupont Circle - Tape Number 6, October 9, 1988; ID: 231.1637A (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1637A)
  - Dupont Circle - Tape Number 7, October 9, 1988; ID: 231.1638 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1638)
  - [1]--Dupont Circle - Tape Number 8 [2]--Fred, October 9, 1988; October 21, 1991; ID: 231.1639A (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1639A)
  - [1]--B-roll of Capitol Building and Quilt, October 9,1988 [2]--VHS Tape Number 1, Washington D.C., October 8, 1988, ID: 231.1640 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1640)
  - Children's Quilt Project - Tape Number 1, October 10, 1988; ID: 231.1641A (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1641A)
    Format: 3/4" Umatic
  - Washington D.C. B-roll, October 10, 1988; ID: 231.1642A (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1642A)
  - Common Threads: Stories From the Quilt, Part 1 of 2, 1988; ID: 231.1643 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1643)
    Duration: 60 minutes
  - Common Threads: Stories From the Quilt, Part 2 of 2, 1988; ID: 231.1644 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1644)
    Duration: 20 minutes
  - Common Threads: Stories of the Quilt, 1988; ID: 231.1645 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1645)
    Duration: 80 minutes
  - The Names Project, AIDS Quilt Public Service Announcement Number 1, September 16, 1996; ID: 231.1646 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1646)
  - The Names Project, AIDS Quilt Public Service Announcement Number 2, September 16, 1996; ID: 231.1647 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1647)
  - Names Project Public Service Announcement Selection, circa 1985-1999; ID: 231.1648 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1648)
  - [1]--Washington Quilt [2]--Mr. Leather New York, Undated; ID: 231.1649 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.1649)
    Program content: David Ranada's Camera
  - Universal Studios Florida, World AIDS Day Candlelight Ceremony and AIDS Memorial Quilt, December 1, 1996; ID: 231.2163 (Box 103, Media ID: 231.2163)
    Duration: 11 minutes
    Program content: B-roll, Dub with AMOL
- Series III: Be Our Guest
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 1, Rollerena, April 4, 1988; ID: 231.0912 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0912)
    Duration: 28 minutes
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 2, Baby Jane Hudson, April 11, 1988; ID: 231.0913 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0913)
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 3, Sybil Bruncheon, April 25, 1988; ID: 231.0914 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0914)
    Duration: 28 minutes; Preservation note: tape damage from 19:00-25:00
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 4, Jack Pedota, May 2, 1988; ID: 231.0915 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0915)
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 6, Gloria Swanson, May 23, 1988; ID: 231.0916 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0916)
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 7, Bela Lugosi, May 30, 1988; ID: 231.0917 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0917)
    Duration: 28 minutes; Preservation note: Tape break around 7 minutes
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 8, Richard Cook, June 6, 1988; ID: 231.0918 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0918)
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 9, Jack Wrangler, June 13, 1988; ID: 231.0919 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0919)
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 11, Jessica Hahn, June 27, 1988; ID: 231.0920 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0920)
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 12, Rollerena, July 4, 1988; ID: 231.0921 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0921)
    Related Materials
    Re-Air of 231.0912
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 13, Baby Jane Hudson, July 11, 1988; ID: 231.0922 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0922)
    Re-Air of 231.0913
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 14, Sybil Bruncheon, July 18, 1988; ID: 231.0923 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0923)
    Re-Air of 231.0914
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 15, Jack Pedota, July 25, 1988; ID: 231.0924 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0924)
    Re-Air of 231.0915
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 16, Andy Humm, August 8, 1988; ID: 231.0925 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0925)
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 17-18, Bela Lugosi, August 15, 1988; ID: 231.0926 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0926)
    Duration: 28 minutes; Preservation note: no control track or video after 5 minutes, but audio remains
    Re-Air of 231.0917
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 19, Richard Cook, August 22, 1988; ID: 231.0927 (Box 59, U-matic ID: 231.0927)
    Duration: 28 minutes; Preservation note: Tape damage at 07:00, 10:30, 11:00
    Re-Air of 231.0918
  - Be My Guest No. 20, Jack Wrangler, August 29, 1988; ID: 231.0928 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0928)
    Duration: 28 minutes; Preservation note: color burst is damaged so image is black and white
    Re-Air of 231.0191
  - Be My Guest No. 20, Angela Lansbury, October 10, 1988; ID: 231.0929 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0929)
    Duration: 28 minutes; Preservation note: tape damage at 06:22 and 15:30, audio goes to low levels at 20:00
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 21, Mae West, October 17, 1988; ID: 231.0930 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0930)
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 22, Hermione Gingold, October 24, 1988; ID: 231.0931 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0931)
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 23, The Wicked Queen from Snow White, October 31, 1988; ID: 231.0932 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0932)
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 24, Noel Coward, November 7, 1988; ID: 231.0933 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0933)
  - Be My Guest Vol. I No. 25, Marlene Dietrich, November 21, 1988; ID: 231.0934 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0934)
  - Be Our Guest Vol. I No. 26, Ruth Gordon, November 28, 1988; ID: 231.0935 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0935)
  - Be My Guest December Vol. I No. 27, Kate Hepburn, April 5, 1988; ID: 231.0936 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0936)
  - Be Our Guest Vol. I No. 28, Bette Midler, December 12, 1988; ID: 231.0937 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0937)
  - Be Our Guest Vol. I No. 29, Tallulah Bankhead, December 19, 1988; ID: 231.0938 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0938)
  - Be Our Guest Vol. I No. 30, Quentin Crisp, December 26, 1988; ID: 231.0939 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0939)
  - Be Our Guest Vol. II No. 1, Sybil Bruncheon, January 2, 1989; ID: 231.0940 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0940)
  - Be Our Guest Vol. II No. 2, Louis Baldonieri, January 9, 1989; ID: 231.0941 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0941)
  - Be Our Guest Vol. II No. 3, Hermione Gingold, January 16, 1989; ID: 231.0942 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0942)
  - Be Our Guest Vol. II No. 4, The Wicked Queen from Snow White, January 23, 1989; ID: 231.0943 (Box 60, U-matic ID: 231.0943)
  - Be Our Guest Vol. II No. 5, Hermione Gingold, January 30, 1989; ID: 231.0944 (Box 61, U-matic ID: 231.0944)
  - Be Our Guest, Opening Night at More Men, Opening Night at Get Out and Give (Mondays at the Limelight), January 17, 1990; ID: 231.0970 (Box 62, U-matic ID: 231.0970)
    Duration: 30 minutes
  - Be Our Guest, Club Night, February 26, 1990; ID: 231.0975 (Box 62, U-matic ID: 231.0975)
  - Be Our Guest, 3/5/1990, ID: 231.0976 (Box 63, U-matic ID: 231.0976)
    Program content: "Houston"
  - Be Our Guest, 3/12/1990, March 12, 1990; ID: 231.0977
    TRT: 00:29:00
    Program content: "Night of 1000 Gowns"
    - Original Recording (Box 63, U-matic 231.0977)
    - DigiBeta Preservation Copy (Box Shared Fales PM 74)
    - DVD Preservation Copy (Box Shared Fales PM 74)
    - DVD Preservation Copy (Box Shared Fales PM 74)
  - Be Our Guest, 3/19/1990, ID: 231.0978 (Box 63, U-matic ID: 231.0978)
    Program content: "Quick!"
  - [1]--Be Our Guest, 3/26/1990 [2]--Health and Fitness with Jessie, 12/18, ID: 231.0979 (Box 63, U-matic ID: 231.0979)
    Program content: "Hot Rods"
    Duration: 30 minutes; Preservation note: This tape was incubated and transferred with dropouts.
  - Be Our Guest, 4/2/1990, ID: 231.0980 (Box 63, U-matic ID: 231.0980)
    Program content: Chip Duckett Birthday, Sister Paula, Cookin' with Esther
  - Be Our Guest, 4/9/1990, ID: 231.0981 (Box 63, U-matic ID: 231.0981)
    Program content: "The Monster"
  - Be Our Guest, 4/16/1990, ID: 231.0982 (Box 63, U-matic ID: 231.0982)
    Program content: "The Thief, The Cook, His Wife, and Her Lover" Party Plus Jimmy Summerville "Read My Lips" American Release Party
  - [1]--Be Our Guest, 4/23/1990 [2]--Health and Fitness with Jessie, 2/19, ID: 231.0983 (Box 63, U-matic ID: 231.0983)
    Program content: [1]--"Bette Davis Auction," "Quick! Art," "Puppet Poly Clinic"
  - Be Our Guest, 4/30/1990, ID: 231.0984 (Box 63, Media ID: 231.0984)
    Program content: Earth Day - B-52s, Ridiculous Theater, Der Ring Gott Farblonjet
  - Be Our Guest, 5/7/1990, ID: 231.0985 (Box 63, Media ID: 231.0985)
    Program content: "GLAAD Media Awards"
  - Be Our Guest, 5/14/1990, ID: 231.0986 (Box 63, U-matic ID: 231.0986)
    Program content: "Quick Party for Longtime Companion," "Without You I'm Nothing"
  - [1]--Be Our Guest, 5/21/1990 [2]--Health and Fitness with Jessie, 12/25, ID: 231.0987 (Box 63, U-matic ID: 231.0987)
    Program content: [1]--"The Roxy"
  - Be Our Guest, 5/29/1990, ID: 231.0988 (Box 63, Media ID: 231.0988)
    Program content: "ACT-Up at the NIH"
  - Be Our Guest, 6/11/1990, ID: 231.0989 (Box 63, U-matic ID: 231.0989)
    Program content: "New Jimies, Quick, and La Palace"
  - [1]--Be Our Guest, 6/18/1990 [2]--Health and Fitness with Jessie, 2/5, ID: 231.0990 (Box 63, U-matic ID: 231.0990)
    Program content: "Channel 69"
  - Be Our Guest, 6/25/1990, ID: 231.0991 (Box 63, U-matic ID: 231.0991)
    Program content: "Pyramid Club," "Channel 69," Strip-o-Grame
  - Be Our Guest, 7/2/1990, ID: 231.0992 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.0992)
    Program content: "Channel 69," "Garden Party"
  - Be Our Guest, 7/9/1990, ID: 231.0993 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.0993)
    Program content: "Indiana Gay Pride," La Cage
  - [1]--Be Our Guest, 7/16/1990 [2]--Health and Fitness with Jessie, 1/15, ID: 231.0994 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.0994)
    Program content: [1]--"Zest"
  - Be Our Guest, 7/23/1990, ID: 231.0995 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.0995)
    Program content: Second Annual Hi-NRG Awards
  - Be Our Guest, 7/30/1990, ID: 231.0996 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.0996)
    Program content: Grace Jones at Palladium
  - Be Our Guest, 8/6/1990, ID: 231.0997 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.0997)
    Program content: More Grace Jones
  - Be Our Guest, 8/13/1990, ID: 231.0998 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.0998)
    Program content: "Monster Show"
  - Be Our Guest, 8/20/1990, ID: 231.0999 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.0999)
    Program content: "Roller Roxy," "Terry Sweeny"
    Duration: 30 minutes; Preservation note: This tape was incubated.
  - [1]--Be Our Guest, 8/27/1990 [2]--Health and Fitness with Jessie, 5/20, ID: 231.1000 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.1000)
    Program content: [1]--"Sod O Mee"
  - Be Our Guest, 9/3/1990, ID: 231.1001 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.1001)
    Program content: "P-Town"
  - [1]--Be Our Guest, 9/10/1990 [2]--Health and Fitness with Jessie, 11/6, ID: 231.1002 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.1002)
    Program content: [1]--"Phoebe LeGere at the Duplex"
  - Be Our Guest, 9/17/1990, September 17, 1990; ID: 231.1003
    Program content: Hosanna, RazorSharp, Wigstock
    - Original Recording (Box 64, U-matic 231.1003)
    - DigiBeta Preservation Copy (Box Shared Fales PM 74)
    - DVD Preservation Copy (Box Shared Fales PM 74)
    - DVD Preservation Copy (Box Shared Fales PM 74)
  - [1]--Be Our Guest, 9/24/1990 [2]--Health and Fitness with Jessie, 2/6, ID: 231.1004 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.1004)
    Program content: [1]--"Jackie Hoffman at Don't Tell Mama"
  - Be Our Guest, 11/15/1990, ID: 231.1005 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.1005)
    Program content: "Steven Broadway Indiscreet Pleasures"
  - Be Our Guest, 11/22/1990, ID: 231.1006 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.1006)
    Program content: "Halloween 1990"
  - Be Our Guest, 11/29/1990, ID: 231.1007 (Box 64, U-matic ID: 231.1007)
  - Be Our Guest, 12/6/1990, ID: 231.1008 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1008)
    Program content: "Monster Show Part II"
  - Be Our Guest, 12/13/1990, December 13, 1990; ID: 231.1009
    Program content: 7th On Sale, Red Hot and Blue
    - Original Recording (Box 65, U-matic 231.1009)
    - DigiBeta Preservation Copy (Box Shared Fales PM 74)
    - DVD Preservation Copy (Box Shared Fales PM 74)
    - DVD Preservation Copy (Box Shared Fales PM 74)
  - The Best of Be Our Guest, 12/19/1990, ID: 231.1010 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1010)
  - Be Our Guest, 12/20/1990, ID: 231.1011 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1011)
    Program content: The Erotic Baker, The Roasting of Candida
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 2, 1/10/1991, ID: 231.1012 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1012)
    Program content: New Years, Wessel O'Connor Gallery
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 4, 1/24/1991, ID: 231.1013 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1013)
    Program content: History of Pornography
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 5, 1/31/1991, January 31, 1991; ID: 231.1014
    Program content: Day of Desperation, Donald Moffet at Wessel
    - Original Recording (Box 65, U-matic 231.1014)
    - DigiBeta Preservation Copy (Box Shared Fales PM 74)
    - DVD Preservation Copy (Box Shared Fales PM 74)
    - DVD Preservation Copy (Box Shared Fales PM 74)
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 6, 2/7/1991, ID: 231.1015 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1015)
    Program content: Edwin Grey, Jimmy Somerville Video Premiere
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 8, 2/21/1991, ID: 231.1016 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1016)
    Program content: "Chicken Delight," Interview with John Glines, "Unfinished Song," Jimmy Somerville
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 10, 3/7/1991, ID: 231.1017 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1017)
    Program content: "Gay Montreal"
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 12, 3/21/1991, ID: 231.1018 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1018)
    Program content: "Sexhibition," "Gran Fury and PONY at New Museum," "Wessel O'Connor," "Jimmy Somerville"
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 14, 4/4/1991, ID: 231.1019 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1019)
    Program content: "Homo Love Moose Song"
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 16, 4/18/1991, ID: 231.1020 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1020)
    Program content: Photos. Remsen Wolf, Greggory Birthday
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 17, 4/25/1991, ID: 231.1021 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1021)
    Program content: Sticky Moments, Homosexual Acts
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 18, 5/2/1991, ID: 231.1022 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1022)
    Program content: "Advice from a Caterpillar," Julian Clary Part 2
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 19, 5/9/1991, ID: 231.1023 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 231.1023)
    Program content: High Strung, Genre, Comrade
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 20, 5/16/1991, ID: 231.1024 (Box 66, U-matic ID: 231.1024)
    Program content: Haunted Host, Angel and Dragon
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 21, 5/23/1991, ID: 231.1025 (Box 66, U-matic ID: 231.1025)
    Program content: Wessel O'Connor, Nesbitt, Bonicatti
  - Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 23, 6/6/1991, ID: 231.1026 (Box 66, U-matic ID: 231.1026)
    Program content: "Hunchback," "Rainbow Run," "Love Ball 2"
  - [1]--Be Our Guest Vol. IX No. 24, 6/13/1991 [2]--Health and Fitness with Jessie, 11/13, ID: 231.1027 (Box 66, U-matic ID: 231.1027)
    Program content: [1]--"Pageant," "AIDS Timeline," "Witney"